starpulse.com 2015-12-25

# Privacy - Starpulse.com

Last Updated Date: **January 30th, 2014**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Starpulse Terms of Use the terms “ **Starpulse** ,” “ **we** ,” and “ **us** ” each includes Media Holdings, LLC and our affiliates and subsidiaries. The Privacy Policy explains how Starpulse may:

  * collect,
  * use, and
  * disclose

information we obtain through the “Service.”

The “ **Service** ” means any website, mobile application, or Internet service under the control of Starpulse, whether partial or otherwise, in connection with providing an online platform for the Starpulse service.

“ **Personal Information** ” means information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you, such as: name, address, email address, or phone number. We do not consider Personal Information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not allow a third party to easily identify a specific individual.

**THE SERVICE COLLECTS YOUR INFORMATION**

We collect Personal Information when you: 

  * register to use the Service;
  * log in with social networking credentials;
  * use the Service; and
  * communicate with us.

We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies, server logs, and other similar technology as you use the Service. 

**Personal Information Collection**. You may register to use some features of the Service. To register, you may need to provide Personal Information, such as your email address and password. You will also create a username. You may also provide other optional information, including but not limited to: username, password, mailing address, email address, age, gender.

**Social Sign-On**. We collect Personal Information from the social media website when you use your social media credentials to log into the Service. For example, when you log in with your Facebook credentials, we may collect the Personal Information you have made publicly available in Facebook, such as your name and profile picture. We may also obtain other information with your permission, such as your Facebook page address, username, password, mailing address, email address, age, gender, and any other related information made available through the social sign-on process or Service.

**Using the Service**. We collect information you post through the Service. For example: when you interact with other users by commenting on stories, submitting a Contribution, or messaging other users through the service. The Service will collect the information you provide in such submissions, including any Personal Information.

**Making Payments**. When you make payments through the Service, you may need to provide Personal Information to our third-party service providers, such as your credit card number. We do not collect your credit card number, but you will be subject to the privacy policy of any third party service provider.

**Customer Support**. We may collect Personal Information through your communications with our customer-support team.

**Location Information from Your Mobile Device**. With your consent, we will collect and store your location information from your mobile device. Collection of this information may improve the provision of the Service.

**Cookies, Automatic Data Collection, and Related Technologies**. The Service collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you use it, including your preferences and anonymous usage statistics.

When you visit the Service, we and our third-party service providers receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, as well as from cookies and similar technology. Cookies are small text files placed in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies. However, if you do that, the Service may not work properly.

By using the Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse, and retain data related to the provision of the Service.

**HOW STARPULSE USES YOUR INFORMATION**

We use Personal Information to 

  * facilitate and improve our services; and
  * communicate with you.

We may use aggregate information for any purpose, including for marketing purposes. 

**Internal and Service-Related Usage**. We use information, including Personal Information, for internal and service-related purposes only and may provide it to third parties to allow us to facilitate the Service. We may use and retain any data we collect to provide and improve our services.

**Communications**. We may send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance.

**Marketing**. We may use information, including Personal Information, to provide online advertising on the Service and to facilitate transmittal of information that we believe may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you.

**Aggregate Data**. We may anonymize and aggregate data collected through the Service and use it for any purpose.

**STARPULSE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share your information: 

  * with our third-party service providers;
  * to comply with legal obligations;
  * to protect and defend our rights and property; and
  * with your permission.

We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission. 

**We Use Vendors and Service Providers**. We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of the Service.

**Displaying to Other Users**. The content you post to the Service may be displayed on the Service.  Additionally, you may elect to use functionality in the Service to post information to social media services such as Facebook and Twitter. Other users of the Service may be able to see some information about you, such as your comments.  We are not responsible for privacy practices of the other users who will view and use the information you post to the Service or that you post to social media services.  You may adjust your privacy settings by editing your profile on the Service. To control who can view information you post to social media services, you should check the privacy settings on those social media services.

**Publication to Social Media Services**. You may elect to use functionality in the Service to post information to social media services such as Facebook and Twitter. If you elect to use this functionality, other users of service and the social media service may see some information about you included in such posted information.

**Marketing**. We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission. We may allow access to other data collected by the Service to enable the delivery of online advertising on this website, or otherwise facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you.

**Our Customers**. We only provide data to our customers after we have removed your Personal Information or have combined it with other people's data in a way that it is no longer associated with you.

**As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures**. We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: comply with law enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; respond to your requests; or protect your, our or others’ rights, property, or safety.

**Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers**. Although we have no present intention to sell Starpulse to a third party, take the company public, go into bankruptcy or surrender control of the company, it is always possible that future circumstances may change that and result in a change in control, merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of assets, or transition of the Service to another provider.  In such an event, or in the event of financing due diligence, your information may be disclosed, sold, or transferred as part of such a transaction, as permitted by law and/or contract.  The use of your Personal Information following any of the foregoing events should be governed by the provisions of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Personal Information was collected.

**With your Permission**. We may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We take steps in an effort to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, neither the Internet nor the Service can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional or unauthorized disclosures.

By using the Service or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Service. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Service or sending an email to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), please notify us through our contact page to the Privacy Department.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 and we do not want it. We will take steps to delete it if we learn we have collected it. 

We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under 13 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed to children under the age of 13. If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you may alert us by directing your inquiry through our contact page to the Privacy Department. If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**

By using the Service, you will transfer data to the United States. 

By choosing to visit the Service or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the State of Connecticut and the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with Starpulse or the Service will be in accordance with the Terms of Use.

**If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and processing globally. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy.**

**UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION OR POSE A QUESTION OR SUGGESTION**

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to us through your use of the Service or otherwise, or if you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please alert us by directing your inquiry through our contact page to the Privacy Department.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES**

We may revise this Privacy Policy, so review it periodically. 

**Posting of Revised Privacy Policy**. We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted. If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically.

**New Uses of Personal Information**. From time to time, we may desire to use or disclose Personal Information in ways not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our practices change regarding previously collected Personal Information in a way that would be materially less restrictive than stated in the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collected the information, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent to any such uses as may be required by law.

**Contact Information**

_Mailing Address:_

Media Holdings, LLC  
25 Business Park Drive  
Branford, Connecticut 06405

 _Email:_

You may alert us by directing your inquiry through our contact page to the Privacy Department.
